Guide to the Nate Brown Western Sound Archive Collection ARS.0124
Archive of Recorded Sound
- 1272. Michelangeli, Piano, 1958-1966; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1274. Furtwangler, 1951-1954; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1278. Mengelberg, Concertgebouw, Michelangeli, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1279. Mengelberg, Walter, Concertgebouw, 1936-1943; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1280. Samuel, Oakland Symphony, Entremont, 1968-01; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1287. Horenstein, Finnish Radio Orchestra. Mahler, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1288. [unidentified, continuation of 1287?], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1297. Britten, English Chamber Orchestra. Aldeburgh Festival, 1968-10-06; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1298. Rostropovich. Aldeburgh Festival, 1968-06-17; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1301. Walter, NY Philharmonic. Bruckner Ninth. Master, 1946; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1301A. Schnabel, Wallenstein. Mozart Piano Concerto No.24, 1946-01-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1301B. Walter, NY Philharmonic, 1946-03-17; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1301C. Walter, NY Philharmonic, 1946-03-10; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1301D. Walter, NY Philharmonic, 1946-03-17; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1302A. Walter, NY Philharmonic, 1944-05-14; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1302B. Walter, NY Philharmonic, 1944-05-07; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1302C. Walter, NY Philharmonic, 1944-05-07; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- [no number, likely 1303-1305]. Kleiber, NBC Symphony 12/20/47; Mengelberg, Concertgebouw 12/12/40, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1306. Sevitzky, NBC Symphony 6/9/46; Rodzinsky, NY Philharmonic 3/31/46, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1307. Schmidt-Isserstedt, SF Symphony, 1967-02-17; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1311. USSR State Symphony Orchestra, Rostropovitch, 1968-08; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1312. USSR State Symphony Orchestra, 1968-08; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1314. Stern, Rose, Davis, BBC Symphony, 1968; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1315. Klemperer, Philharmonia, 1961-11-27; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1316. Dorati, Stockholm Philharmonic 5/1/68; Kleiber, Vienna Symphony; Thallaug, Eyron; Celibidache, Swedish Radio Orchetra, Nilsson 9/1/68; Richter, Britten. Aldeburgh 1968; Bernstein, NY Philharmonic 9/26/68; Erikson, Eyron, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 11)
- 1321. Rignold, City of Birmingham Symphony, Rostropovich, 1968-09-18; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1322. Amadeus Quartet, Britten, Rostropovich. Edinburgh Festival, 1968; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1323. Bernstein, NY Philharmonic, 1968-09-19; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1324. Boulez, BBC Symphony, 1968; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1325. Serkin Recital, RFH, 1968-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1326. Boult, New Philharmonia, Gilels, 1967; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1327. [Boult, New Philharmonia, Gilels?], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1328. [Boult, New Philharmonia, Gilels?], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1329. Birmingham Symphony, Rostropovich. Britten Cello Symphony, Haydn Cello Concerto; Newstone, Haymarket Orchestra. Satie, Jack in the Box; Brymer, BBC Welsh Orchestra. Milhaud, Scaramouche, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1331. Ehrling, Westerberg, Swedish Radio Orchestra. Berwald, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1347. Scherchen, BBC Symphony Orchestra. September 27, October 2; Cameron, RPO, 1952; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1353. Michelangeli. Carnegie Hall, 1968-11-26; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1355. Bustabo. Bruch, Violin Concerto 10/27/40. Schubert, Rosamunde 11/27/41; Giesekin. Rachmaninoff, Piano Concerto No.2 10/31/40, 1940-1941; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1357. Goldberg, BBC Symphony, 1968-11-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1358. Goldberg Concert, 1968-11-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1361. Giulini, NY Philharmonic, Michelangeli 1/13/68; Ormandy, Philadelphia Orchestra, Kapell 12/1/45, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1363. Sternfeld, Belgian Radio and Television Orchestra, Gertler; Dmitriadi, Moscow State Symphony, Rostropovich 2/23/69; Dennis Brain Wind Ensemble, BBC, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1364. Menuhin, LSO. Edinburgh Festival; Boult, LSO, Milstein RFH, 1968; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1365. Menuhin, London Festival, 1968-07-09; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1366. Koussevitsky, BSO 1945; Hansen, Rochester Orchestre; Goosens, Cleveland Orchestra; Ormandy, Philadelphia Orchestra, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1371. Melos Ensemble, BBC; Andre Marchal; Matias, Chamber Soloists of Czechoslovakia, Schwetzingen Festival 1968; Dorati, BBC Choir and Symphony; Smetana Quartett. Praha Festival 1968; Westerberg, Swedish Radio Orchestra; Musica Molmiae; Arrau, Bergen Festival 1968; Kertesz, Stockholm Philharmonic; Ericson, Sweish Radio Choir; Boehm, Vienna Philharmonic. Salzburg 1968; Kogan, Nahum, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1372. Mitropoulos, NY Philharmonic, 1955-04-10; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1373. Monteux, BSO. Tanglewood WQXR, 1962; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1375. Walter, NY Philharmonic, Schnabel, 1941-11-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1379. Krenz, DSRSO, Michelangeli, 1966-05-27; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1380. Milhaud, Bavarian Radio Symphony Orchestra [etc.], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1381. Stokowski, NY Philharmonic, Hess [crossed out], 1949-02-06; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1386. Deutsche Welle Master Dubs, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1386A. Rosbaud, SWR Orchestra [From DW Masters], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1389. Davis, BBC Symphony, Rubinstein [etc.], 1968-12-04; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1391. Van Vactor, Chilean Symphony; Whitney, Chilean Orchestra; Tevah, Chamber Orchestra, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1392. Schmidt-Isserstedt, Chicago Symphony 10/17-18; Martinon, Chicago Symphony, Helffer 10/31 -11/1, 1968; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1392 (2). Klemperer, Vienna Philharmonic. Vienna Festival, 1968; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 12)
- 1393. Edinburgh Festival [etc.], 1968; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1398. Dub of Schnabel, Beethoven 4th, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1400. Rostropovich Recital, With A. Dedukhin, 1969-05-02; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1403. Rubinstein Interview [etc.], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1404. Solti, Vienna Philharmonic, 1969-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1405. Mengelberg, Concertgebouw [Philips Japan FL-5570]; Enesco, Orchestra des Concerts Colonne [Remington R-199-207], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1409. Goldberg, BBC Symphony 3/29/69; Boult's 80th Birthday Concert, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1417. Rostropovich, Brooklyn Academy, 1969-05-06; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1425. Wagner, Die Feen (BBC 5/22/63); Freischutz (Vienna 1933), 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1426. Sibelius Festival, 1964; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1427. Katims, Seattle Symphony, 1959-04; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1429. Schmidt-Isserstedt, Cleveland Orchestra, 1969-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1430. Poliuto, La Scala, 1960-12-07; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1431. Kubelik, Chicago Symphony, Johannesen, 1969-01; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1432. Kubelik, Chicago Symphony, Johannesen, 1969-01; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1433. Kubelik, Chicago Symphony, 1969-01; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1434. Kubelik, Chicago Symphony, 1969-01; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1441. Rostropovich, Dedukhin. Carnegie Hall, 1969-05-02; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1442. Rostropovich, Dedukhin. Carnegie Hall, 1969-05-02; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1445. Goldberg, BBC Symphony; Maderna, Darmstadt Chamber Orchestra, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1446. Hurst, BBC Northern Symphony, York Festival Choir, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1450. Stokowski, Hollywood Bowl, Grainger, 1945-07-15; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1457. Stravinsky, Craft, Israel Philharmonic. Israel Festival, 1962.; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1458. Fritz Busch Tape No.1, 1933-1951; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1459. Furtwangler, Vienna Philharmonic 5/2/44; Busch, Danish State Radio Orchestra and Chorus 9/7/50, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1463. Boulez, Blossom Music Festival. Stravinsky, Firebird Suite WAKR, 1969-09-14; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1465. Goldberg, Netherlands Chamber Orchestra [Philips 700-201-WGY]; Carmirelli, Serkin. Marlboro Festival, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1474. Erdmann [Electrola E80947, E80948]; Fasset, Mitropoulos Interview 12/11/49, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1480. Mizerit, Atlantic Symphony Orchestra 6/10/69; Avison, CBC Vancouver Chamber Orchestra 8/10/69 [corr. enclosed], 1969; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1482. Oistrakh, Swedish Radio Orchestra 12/68; Celibidache, SRO 6/28/69; Dorati, Stockholm Philharmonic; Temirkanov, SRO, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1484. Koussevitsky, BSO. AFRS test [crossed out], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1491. Celibidache, SRO, Michelangeli. Helsinki Festival 5/20/69; Rudolf, Cincinnati Orchestra, Rostropovich, 1969; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1496. Milhaud, Protee Suite, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1497. Milhaud, Carewe, London, BBC, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 13)
- 1498. Goldberg, BBC Symphony; Enesco, Boyd Neel Orchestra 1952, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1499. Goldberg, Netherlands Chamber Orchestra, TV; Boult, LPO, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1519. Munch, BSO. Honegger, 1956-04-20; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1520. Michelangeli Recital, BBC, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1522. Turnovsky, Toronto Symphony, Bachauer. CBC 3/3/70; Ancerl, Toronto Symphony CBC 3/12/70, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1523. Ancerl, Toronto Symphony CBC 3/12/70; Polson, Aide CBC 3/11/70, 1970-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1524. Burgos, Toronto Symphony CBC 1/25/70; Salgo, Royal Philharmonic BBC. Searle, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1525. Salgo, Royal Philharmonic BBC; Staryk, Perry CBC 2/12/70, 1970; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1526. Festival De Menton 1a. Muller-Bruhl, Chamber Orchestra of Cologne, 1968; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1527. Festival De Menton 1b. Muller-Bruhn, Chamber Orchestra of Cologne, 1968; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1528. Festival De Menton 2a, 1968; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1529. Festival De Menton 2b, 1968; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1530. Festival De Menton 3, 1968; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1531. Festival D'Aix-en-Provence 4a, 1968; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1532. Festival De La Cote Languedocienne 6a, 1968-07-18; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1533. Festival De La Cote Languedocienne 6b, 1968-07-18; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1534. Festival De La Cote Languedocienne 6c, 1968-07-18; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1535. Walter, RAI (Rome) 5/19/54; Walter, Maggio Musicale Orchestra 5/25/54; NY Philharmonic 12/12/48, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1536. Michelangeli, 1967-1970; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1538. Caracciolo, RAI (Milan), Rostropovich [program enclosed], 1970-04-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1539. Rostropovich Rehearsals, Caracciolo, RAI Milan, 1970-04-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1547. Reiner, NBC Symphony. Carnegie Hall. KGW, 1952-01-19; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1550. Celibidache, Swedish Radio Symphony; Farncombe, SRO; Hagegard, Eyron; Brililioth, Kempff; Royal Swedish Opera Orchestra, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1551. Keilberth, Bamberg Symphony. Furtwangler, Symphony No. 3, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1556. Boulez, Cleveland Orchestra, Marcellus. Toledo, Ohio, 1970-06-28; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1557. Boulez, Cleveland Orchestra. Lakewood, Ohio WCLV, 1970-06-14; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1558. Boulez Lecture, Cleveland, 1970-03-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1562. Monteux, BSO. Tanglewood, 1962; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1563. Monteux, BSO. Tanglewood, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1564. Skrovacewsky, RAI (Turin), Rostropovich 3/20/70; Maazel, Rotterdam Philharmonic. Holland Festival 6/17/69, 1969-1970; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1566. Pope, New Philharmonia, Holmes. Brian, Violin Concerto. BBC, 1969-06-20; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1567. Head, Kensington Symphony, Cook. Brian, Symphony No.5 12/11/69; BBC Symphony, Proms. Bliss, Arnold 8/16/69; Downes, LSO. Brian BBC 1/69, 1969; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1568. Mengelberg, Concertgebouw [Fontana Japan SFON-10605]; Enesco, Orchestra Des Concerts Colonne [Remington R-199-207]; Furtwangler, Berlin Philharmonic [RCA DM-553], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1569. Mitropoulos, NY Philharmonic, Szigeti, 1952-11-16; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1572. Alicia De La Rocha, Hunter College, 1967-10-21; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 14)
- 1576. Szymon Goldberg, Violin; Cantelli, BSO. Schumann, Grainger, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1581. Britten, English Chamber Orchestra. Aldeburgh Festival 1970; Groves, Royal Liverpool Philharmonic, Rostropovich, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1582. Britten, English Chamber Orchestra, Rostropovich. Aldeburgh Festival 1970; Groves, Royal Liverpool Philharmonic, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1583. Goldberg, Northern Sinfonia; Rostropovich, Dedukhin, Yugoslav Radio, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1584. Rostropovich, Yugoslav Radio, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1589. Schoenberg, Five Pieces; Message From Schoenberg, 1949-09-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1590. Karajan, New York Philharmonic. Webern [program enclosed], 1958-11-15; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1591. Maazel, NY Philharmonic. Dallipicolla 3/28/65; Bernstein, NY Philharmonic. Webern 12/5/65, 1965; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1596. Jochum, Bavarian Radio Orchestra, Fischer. Mozart, 1954-12-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1601. Kempe, Bavarian State Orchestra. Strauss Memorial Concert, 1961-09-08; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1603. Wallenstein, Los Angeles Philharmonic, Schnabel, 1946-01-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1604. Barnett, LA Philharmonic, Kapell. Standard Hour, 1951-02-04; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1607. Festival De Lourdes-Tarbes 8a, 1968-04-23; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1608. Festival De Lourdes-Tarbes 8b, 1968-04-23; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1609. Pretre, RAI (Rome), Weissenberg. 5/21/69; Rostropovich, Yugoslav Radio, BBC 4/18/70, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1610. Caracciolo, RAI (Turin), Rostropovich 10/65; Bohm, Vienna Philharmonic. Salzburg Festival 8/23/70, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1611. Radio Nederlands Transcriptions CA-5, CA-6, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1612. Radio Nederlands Transcriptions CA-3, CA-4, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1613. Radio Nederlands Transcriptions CA-9, CA-10, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1614. Radio Nederlands Transcriptions CA-11, CA-12, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1615. Radio Nederlands Transcriptions CA-13, CA-7, CA-8, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1616. Radio Nederlands Transcriptions CA-1, CA-2, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1616. French Radio Transcriptions, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1618. Furtwangler, Berlin Philharmonic, 1944-1953; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1619. Furtwangler, Vienna Philharmonic. Salzburg Festival 8/31/50; Berlin Philharmonic 10/24/48, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1620. Hindeland, Insbruck State Orchestra. Austrian Broadcast, 1963; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1621. Excerpts From Dutch Radio Program, Holland In Art and Music, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1625. Dobrowen, Stockholm Opera, Stockholm Radio Orchestra 1943-1945; Busch, Vienna Tonkunstlerorchester, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1626. Mann, Stockholm Radio Orchestra; Stockholm Philharmonic; Busch, Vienna Tonkunstlerorchester, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1628. Previtali, NY Philharmonic, Menuhin 12/12/57; Appia, OSR, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1636. Segerstam, Swedish Radio Symphony, Nilsson 1/3/70; Ehrling, Swedish Radio Symphony Orchestra; Del Mar, Gothenberg Symphony Orchestra 4/70; Miedel, SRO 1970; Commissiona, Gothenberg Symphony Orchestra 1969; International C-Trio; Kubelik, Bavarian Radio Orchestra and Choir 1970; Ohrwall, Musica Holmiae 10/24/70, 1969-1970; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1639. Busch Quartet. South German Radio, BBC 8/21/70; Edwin Fischer, Piano. North German Radio, BBC 5/2/70, 1970; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1640. Rodzinski, NY Philharmonic, Hofmann c1948; Kletski, Dallas Symphony 1/59, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1641. Mehta, LA Philharmonic, 1971-01; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1642. Busch Quartet, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1644. Koussevitsky, BSO 1/4/47, 3/2/48, 4/48; Monteux, SF Symphony 4/48, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1647. Samuel, LA Philharmonic, 1971-03-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 15)
- 1648. Samuel, LA Philharmonic, 1971-03-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1649. Enesco, NY Philharmonic, 1937-01-31; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1649A. Enesco, NY Philharmonic. Carnegie Hall, 1937-01-31; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1656. Furtwangler, Berlin Philharmonic 5/14/53; Furtwangler, South German Radio Orchestra. BBC, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1657. Semkow, Cleveland Orchestra, Harrell. WCLV, 1971-05-09; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1659. Festival de Saint-Maximin 5, 1968-07-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1660. Festival de Paris 9b. Cape, Brussells Pro Musica Antiqua, 1968; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1661. Festival de Paris 9a, 1968; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1665. Rudolph Ringwall Remembers, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1666. Giora Bernstein, Claremont Music Festival Orchestra. Beethoven, Violin Concerto [program enclosed], 1971-07-02; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1667. Walter, NY Philharmonic. Carnegie Hall, 1943-11-07; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1674. Mitropoulos, Chavez, NY Philharmonic, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1677. Paul Hindemith, Cologne Radio Orchestra, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1688. De Sabata, Pittsburgh Symphony. Strauss, Don Quixote, 1949; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1694. Tzipine, ORTF Orchestra; Quartet ORTF. Saint-Saens, 1970; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1695. State Opera Dresden Orchestra [etc.], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1697. Ansermet, NBC Symphony. Bartok; Stravinsky, 1949-01-08; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1698. Ansermet, NBC Symphony. Bach; Honegger; Ravel, 1948-12-18; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1699. Ansermet, NBC Symphony. Humperdinck; Schubert, 1948-12-25; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1702. Swedish Radio Symphony Orchestra; Stockholm Philharmonic [etc.], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1703. Rostropovich, Dudekin. Massey Hall, Toronto [program enclosed], 1972-02-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1704. Rostropovich, Dudekin. Massey Hall, Toronto, 1972-02-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1705. Schnabel Pupils, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1705A. Encores From Rostropovich Recitals. Hunter College 1/31/72; Philharmonic Hall 12/8/71, 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 32)
- 1706. Bellugi, RAI (Milan), Rostropovich, 1967-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1707. Ormandy, NBC Symphony. Carnegie Hall, 1952-01-26; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1708. Ceccato, Cleveland Orchestra. De Sabata, Juventus. WCLV, 1972-01; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1709. Ansermet. Mozart, Linz Symphony; Foss, Ricordare, 1950-02-04; 1 7" open reel tape (paper tape) (Audio 16)
- 1715. Goldberg; Boult, LPO 5/10/72, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1718. Furtwangler, Berlin Philharmonic. Rome, 1951-05-01; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1720. Furtwangler, Berlin Philharmonic. Bruckner pt.1, 1949-03-15; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1721. Strauss, Orchestra Radio Suizzera Italiana, Brun, 1947-07-25; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1721 (2). Furtwangler, BPO. Bruckner pt.2, 1949; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1722. Stock, Chicago Symphony 4/9/38; Menuhins. Mozart 12/19/37, 1937-1938; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1724. Michelangeli Recital, Warsaw, 1955-03-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1725. Michelangeli, Recital Warsaw 3/13/55; Inbal, RAI (Milan), Pollini 1967, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1728. Stravinsky, NY Philharmonic. Rite of Spring, 1940-04-07; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1729. Stravinsky, NY Philharmonic. Rite of Spring, Petrochka Suite, 1940-04-07; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 16)
- 1730. Lucerne Festival [crossed out], 1954-08-22; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1731. Lucerne Festival [crossed out], 1954-08-22; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1770. Celibidache, Temirkanov, Westerberg, Genetay, SRS 1972; Blomstedt, Stockholm Philharmonic 3/22/72, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1783. Elly Ney and the Beethoven Concertos, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1790. Haskil-Schuridt, Stuttgart Radio. Mozart, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1804. Rostropovich. USSR Symphony 8/21/68; Sargent, BBC Symphony, Proms, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1805. Giulini, Philharmonia, Rostropovich. Edinburgh Festival 9/6/62; Gibson, Scottish National Orchestra, Rostropovich 1966, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1810. Furtwangler, RAI (Turin), Da Vito. Mendelssohn, 1952-03-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1819. Heimans, Maastrichts Stedelijk Orkest, Gieseking. Liszt, Concerto in E-flat, 1940-11-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 1822. Klemperer, New Friends of Music. Town Hall WQXR, 1942-12-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1823. Rubinstein Carnegie Hall Concert 4/11/50; Katims, NBC Symphony 8/6/47, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1828. Kolisch. Bartok Quartet No.5, 1941-01-26; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1846. Pollini, de Burgos, Toronto Symphony, 1973-02-09; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1851. SODRE Orchestra. Beethoven Symphony No.6 7/22/39. J. Strauss, Harmonie 11/8/38; BPO. Brahms, Haydn Variations 5/54; VPO. Beethoven Leonore No.5 2/5/44; Furtwangler, VPO 5/8/43, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1852. Klieber, SODRE Orchestra and Chorus. Beethoven, Symphony No.9 8/12/39; Furtwangler, BPO. Weber, Euryanthe 1954; Kleiber, SODRE Orchestra. Strauss, Blue Danube 11/8/38, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1853. Goldberg, Pittsburgh Symphony. Berg, Violin Concerto, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1869. Busch, Swedish Radio Orchestra Rehearsal 5/51; Rodzinski, NY Philharmonic, Huberman 11/17/46, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1877. Tilson Thomas, BSO 5/11/74; Horowitz Press Conference WCLV, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1895. Fritz Stiedry Haydn Acetates [corr. enclosed], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1898. Reiner, Cleveland Symphony. Prokofiev; Sibelius, 1955-02-27; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1900. Walter, NY Philharmonic, Hess, 1951-02-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1902. Rodzinski, NY Philharmonic 10/22/44, 10/28/45; Rodzinski, Cleveland Symphony 1/9/43, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1903. Rodzinski, NY Philharmonic, Szantho. Mahler, Symphony No.2, 1943-12-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1923. Bach Aria with Fischer-Diesau, Menuhin, Puyana, Rostropovich; Szymon Goldberg, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1930. Walter, New York Philharmonic, Rubinstein, 1947-02-09; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1933. Schonzeler, Bournemouth Symphony. Bruckner; Deryck Cook Discussing Bruckner's 8th, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1945. Whom The Gods Love 1938; Maazel, Cleveland Symphony, Rostropovich. Pension Fund Concert WCLV 5/11/75, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1948. Furtwangler, Vienna Philharmonic. Salzburg Festival 8/7/49; Salzburg Festival 8/30/54, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1949. Michelangeli Recital, Lugano, 1973-05-21; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)
- 1951. William Kapell. Rachmaninoff, Concerto No.3 (Two Versions), 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 17)